

HITESH NAREDA

hitesh.aiesec@gmail.com +974 6630 7921 I am a highly driven individual with vast international experience, having worked with over a 25 nationalities and cultures within my tenure. I have a true passion for Hospitality from HOH to FOH, managing diversified teams and interaction with guests which I see as my forte in the industry. My Ambition and Passion for Excellence is the key to my success and ensuring the development of my team members to create mutual win-win for my Associates, Organization, Owners and Personal Growth

KEY SKILLS

Operations Management

••••

Front Office and Revenue Management

••••

Owner Management

••••

Sales and Marketing

Human Resource Management

0000

Housekeeping Operations



PROGRAMS

Microsoft Office – Word, PowerPoint, Outlook, Excel

Extranets - Booking.com, TripAdvisor, Expedia, Agoda, MMT, Hotelbeds

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

Currently employed with the Iconic Fairmont Doha solely responsible for 90 Rooms, 2 F&B outlets and a Bar.

A competent professional with over 14 years of experience in Hotel Operations and Management. A true operations specialist – with experience in some of the best luxury resorts and hotels.

Wide experience spanning across resorts, boutique hotels and business hotels in Middle East, Africa and Asia.

Successfully managed the pre-openings for Premier Inn Doha Airport, Four Points by Sheraton, Zubarah Boutique Hotel and re-branding of Sealine Beach Resort.

Expertise on liaising with Qatar Tourism Authority on their licensing and classification requirements

Comprehensive knowledge of budgeting, procurement, inventory maintenance, buying within hotels; sound understanding of hygiene, health, safety regulations.

Change agent with clear understanding of budgets, financial planning, P&L, business requirements and experience of operating numerous units.

Fairmont Doha

CAREER TIMELINE

Sheraton

2010 - 2012
The Westin
Sohna Resort &

2013 – 2016
Zubarah
Boutique Hotel

2018 till 2022
Premier Inn
Doha Airport

2008 - 2010
Four Points by
Speke &

2016 – 2018
Speke &
Sealine Beach

Munyonyo

Commonwealth Resort

EXPERIENCE

Mar 2022 – till Date Fairmont Doha

Aug 2018 – Jan 2022 Premier Inn Doha Airport

2016 - 2018 Katara Hospitality Sealine Beach Resort Doha - Qatar

2013 – 2016 Zubarah Boutique Hotel Doha - Qatar

2012 - 2013 Speke & Munyonyo Commonwealth Resort

Kampala, Uganda

2008 - 2012

Marriott International

The Westin Sohna Resort & Spa

Four Points by Sheraton

Jaipur, Gurugram - India

FAIRMONT GOLD OPERATIONS MANAGER

Pre-opening the Iconic Fairmont Doha – In charge of 90 Rooms, a Restaurant, a Bar and the Fairmont Gold Pool.

Recruitment, outlet and venue setup, procurement, formulating Standard Operating procedures and guidelines

OPERATIONS MANAGER

Hotelier Middle East – Highly Commended Hotel – 2021 award (from over 100 hotels in GCC)

Pre-opening setup of the second premier inn in Doha – Qatar

Successful in elevating and maintaining the hotel on No. 9.4 rating on Booking.com 99.7% and 99.6% score on NSF Audits

Formulating Room Budget and property budget.

Qatar Clean Certification

FRONT OFFICE MANAGER

Rebranding of the property to Murwab and maintaining high Katara standards throughout, managing inventory and operations and working to achieve the Rooms budget of 38 mn. Qar.

FRONT OFFICE & REVENUE MANAGER

Pre Opening Of the Property and maintaining the service standards, guest ratings and optimizing revenue.

COMPLEX ASSISTANT FRONT OFFICE MANAGER

Managing a team of 48 individuals and managing the inventory of 445 rooms, suites

GROWTH PATH

Sep 2012 to Nov 2013 - Complex Assistant Front Office Manager

Mar 2012 to Sep 2012 - Complex Duty Manager

DUTY MANAGER

GROWTH PATH

Sep 2011 to Mar 2012 - Duty Manager

Aug 2010 to Sep 2011 - Front Office Executive

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Hotel Management Institute of Hotel Management - Jaipur - 2008

TRAINING

Mar 2006 to Sep 2006

ITC Luxury Collection – Sheraton Rajputana

Industrial Trainee

'Letter of Appreciation' from HR & Culinary for outstanding performance during the ICC Champions Trophy Matches.

LANGUAGE

English
Hindi
Urdu
Punjabi
Arabic
French

PERSONAL

Date of Birth: August 4, 1986

Nationality: Indian

Visa Status: Resident Permit - Qatar

Passport Details S9840260

Driving License Qatari and Indian (LMV – Car)